[
    {
        "uid": 0,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: \nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 1,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 2,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 3,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 4,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 5,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, down, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 6,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 7,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 8,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 9,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 10,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 11,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 12,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 13,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 14,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 15,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 16,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 17,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 18,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 19,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 20,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 21,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 22,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 23,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 24,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 25,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 26,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 27,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0\n\nInput: down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 28,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: \nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 29,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 30,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, right, right, down, down, up, up, right, left, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, right, right, left, left, right, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: left, down, left, right, right, right, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, down, left, left, down, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: left, up, up, down, down, up, left, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: right, down, up, down, up, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: left, down, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 1, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, right, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 0, left: 0, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 31,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, left, up, down, right, down, left, right, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, up, left, down, left, left, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 3, right: 0\n\nInput: up, left, up, up, down, left, down, down, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: right, right, right, down, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 0, right: 4\n\nInput: right, down, up, left, right, left, left, up, right, left, down, down, right, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: down, up, left, left, up, down, up, down, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: right, up, right, down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, up, down, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 2, right: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, down, up, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 1, left: 0, right: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 32,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, right, up, down, down, right, right, right, down, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: down, down, right, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: up, down, left, down, down, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, right, down, left, right, left, down, left, up, down, right, left, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: left, up, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, down, down, left, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: down, right, right, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 0, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 1, left: 0, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 33,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: up, left, left, down, down, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 3, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, left, right, right, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, down, right, down, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, right, down, left, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, down, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: up, left, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 2, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, left, down, left, left, left, down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 34,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, up, up, right, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, left, right, right, right, right, left, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: left, down, down, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: right, up, right, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: left, down, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: right, right, right, down, left, down, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, left, down, down, right, right, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: up, left, left, down, right, down, left, right, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, up, right, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 35,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, right, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: right, down, left, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, right, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, right, up, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 0, right: 3\n\nInput: left, down, up, left, down, left, left, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, up, down, right, left, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, down, down, right, right, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 0, right: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 0, left: 1, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 36,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, up, down, up, down, up, up, left, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: right, down, right, left, left, right, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: down, up, right, right, up, right, left, left, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: left, left, right, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, left, down, up, down, up, right, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, up, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 0, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: right, down, down, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, right, right, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 0, left: 0, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 37,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, up, up, down, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, up, down, left, down, up, left, left, down, down, up, right, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: left, down, up, down, down, left, right, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: right, right, right, up, left, left, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, down, up, right, down, up, up, up, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: up, left, down, up, right, right, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: up, left, down, right, up, up, up, left, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: up, right, left, left, down, down, up, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 3, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, up, up, right, right, right, up, left, right, left, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 0, left: 4, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 38,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, right, left, left, down, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: left, up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: down, right, right, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 0, right: 4\n\nInput: down, right, up, up, right, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up, left, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: right, right, left, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: down, up, left, down, right, left, up, up, up, down, down, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 3, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, right, up, left, right, down, down, left, up, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 3, left: 2, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 39,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, right, left, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, right, down, right, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, right, right, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: right, down, up, up, down, up, down, down, right, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: right, up, right, down, right, right, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 0, right: 4\n\nInput: left, right, right, right, down, left, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, right, down, down, up, right, up, down, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 0, right: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, left, right, right, right, down, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 2, left: 2, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 40,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, left, up, left, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: right, left, up, right, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, up, down, left, right, up, down, left, right, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: left, left, down, left, down, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: down, up, right, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: up, left, right, right, down, up, up, up, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, up, left, left, left, right, up, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: left, up, down, left, right, right, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 2, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, left, up, left, left, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 0, left: 4, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 41,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, left, right, right, left, right, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: down, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: up, down, right, down, right, down, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, right, up, down, down, left, right, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: right, right, up, right, down, right, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 0, right: 4\n\nInput: up, right, right, down, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, up, right, up, down, down, down, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0, left: 0, right: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, left, right, right, right, up, left, down, right, down, up, down, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 3, left: 3, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 42,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, down, down, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: right, up, left, down, left, down, right, up, up, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, left, up, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 3, right: 0\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: left, down, down, right, left, down, left, left, up, up, right, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, down, left, right, left, left, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: left, left, left, down, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, left, up, right, right, up, left, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 0, left: 1, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 43,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, right, up, left, down, up, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, right, down, down, right, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, left, left, up, right, down, right, left, right, left, down, right, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: down, right, right, left, down, down, right, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: up, down, left, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: up, up, left, right, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 2, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, down, right, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 1, left: 0, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 44,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, left, right, left, up, down, left, down, left, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: down, down, left, up, right, up, up, right, down, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, left, up, up, up, left, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: down, up, right, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, left, right, down, left, down, up, right, right, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 4, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: left, up, up, down, left, left, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: down, left, up, left, down, up, left, up, right, right, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 3, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, right, down, right, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 2, left: 0, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 45,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, up, up, down, left, right, right, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: right, up, left, left, left, down, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: right, up, down, up, left, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: up, left, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: left, up, down, left, right, up, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, left, left, down, up, left, left, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: left, right, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 46,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, down, down, left, left, up, down, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: down, right, down, right, left, left, right, down, up, up, up, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: down, left, left, up, left, left, down, right, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: down, left, up, left, left, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 3, right: 0\n\nInput: up, up, left, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: down, left, down, down, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: down, left, down, up, up, up, down, up, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, up, left, up, up, down, right, left, right, right, down, left, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 3, left: 3, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 47,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: up, down, right, down, left, right, down, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: right, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, down, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, up, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 4, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, up, right, right, up, up, down, down, left, right, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 2, left: 3, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 48,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, down, left, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, left, left, left, down, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: right, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, up, right, right, right, left, left, up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, right, right, right, up, up, left, left, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: left, left, left, down, down, left, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, left, right, down, right, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, up, down, down, right, up, left, up, left, up, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 4, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, right, down, right, left, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 3, left: 1, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 49,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, up, left, right, up, right, left, left, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: left, left, down, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: down, right, up, down, down, right, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, left, right, up, left, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: right, left, left, up, down, left, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, left, down, left, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 2, right: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, down, left, up, right, down, left, down, down, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 4, left: 2, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 50,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: down, left, left, right, up, left, right, up, up, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: left, down, left, down, up, up, down, up, right, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: up, right, down, left, down, left, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: right, up, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 1, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, up, up, left, left, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 0, left: 3, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 51,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, right, left, up, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, left, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: down, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, right, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, left, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, right, left, right, right, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, up, down, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: left, up, down, up, up, left, up, right, left, down, down, down, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 4, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, up, up, up, down, up, left, right, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, down: 2, left: 1, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 52,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 2, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, right, left, down, down, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: left, down, left, up, left, right, down, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: right, right, right, up, down, down, up, right, up, down, left, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: left, down, down, left, down, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 3, right: 0\n\nInput: up, up, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: left, left, down, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: right, up, up, down, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 1, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, down, right, down, right, down, down, left, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 53,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, left, right, left, up, down, right, right, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: right, right, right, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: up, right, right, up, left, down, up, right, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: right, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, down, left, right, left, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, down, down, up, right, down, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 54,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: down, left, left, left, down, down, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 4, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, up, left, down, down, right, left, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: right, right, left, down, right, left, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: right, down, left, left, left, right, right, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: up, up, left, right, left, right, down, up, left, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 1, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: left, right, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: left, down, down, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 3, left: 1, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, down: 1, left: 0, right: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 55,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, left, right, right, left, up, left, right, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: right, down, right, up, left, down, right, left, right, left, down, up, up, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: down, up, up, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, up, right, left, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, right, up, down, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 3, left: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: left, right, left, right, left, right, down, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: up, up, left, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, left, right, down, left, right, left, left, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 56,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, right, left, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, down: 1, left: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: right, right, up, right, right, left, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 1, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: up, up, left, down, down, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, down, down, right, down, down, left, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, down, up, right, left, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: up, right, up, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 0, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, left, down, left, left, right, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 4, left: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, down, left, down, right, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, down: 4, left: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, left, right, right, down, up, right, down, left, down, right, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, down: 3, left: 4, right: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 57,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, right, left, left, left, up, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: right, left, right, up, right, right, up, up, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 4, down: 0, left: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: down, up, down, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 1, right: 0\n\nInput: right, right, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 0, left: 0, right: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up, right, right, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, left, left, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: left, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, up, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 2, down: 1, left: 0, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, left, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 1, left: 2, right: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 58,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, down, up, up, down, left, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: left, right, right, left, up, right, right, left, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 0, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: up, down, right, down, up, down, down, right, right, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 0, right: 4\n\nInput: up, left, left, up, left, down, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 2, left: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, left, left, right, right, left, right, right, left, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: down, right, left, left, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2, down: 3, left: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, down: 0, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: left, down, up, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 1, right: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, down, down, left, right, right, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, down: 2, left: 2, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 59,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "count-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, down: 0, left: 0, right: 0\n\nInput: down, left, right, right, down, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, down: 2, left: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: right, down, down, down, left, up, up, up, right, left, left\nOutput: up: 3, down: 3, left: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: left, down, up, left, left, right, up, right, up, right, down, down, left, up\nOutput: up: 4, down: 3, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: down, left, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, down: 2, left: 2, right: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, left, left, left, down, down, up, left, down\nOutput: up: 4, down: 4, left: 4, right: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, left, down, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, down: 1, left: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, right, right, right, right, down\nOutput: up: 2, down: 2, left: 0, right: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, down, down, right, right, left, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, down: 2, left: 2, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 60,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 61,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 62,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 63,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 64,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 65,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 66,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 67,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: \nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 68,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 69,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 70,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: \nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 71,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 72,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, down, down, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 73,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, up, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 74,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 75,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 76,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 77,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 78,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 79,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 80,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down, up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 81,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, up, down, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 82,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, up, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 83,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 84,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 85,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 4\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 86,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: up: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 87,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up, down, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: down: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 88,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: down, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 89,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-easy",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4\n\nInput: down, down, up, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: up, up, down, down, up, down, down\nOutput: down: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, down\nOutput: up: 0\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 90,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, right, right, left, up, up, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, right, right, left, down, up\nOutput: down: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, right, left, right, right, down\nOutput: down: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: up, right, down, right, right, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, up, up, left, right, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 4, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, up, down, left, right, right, down, right, left, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 91,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, right, up, left, up, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: left, down, up, up, up, right, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: left, down, up, up, right, right, down, down, down, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, right, up, up, up, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, down, up, right, up, down\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, right, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, down, up, down, down, left, left, up, down, up, left, up, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 3\n\nInput: left, right, left, left, right, up, down, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, left, down, left, right, left, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, left: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 92,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, left, left, right, up, down, right, up, right, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, up, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, up, up, left, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: up, down, left, up, left, left, down, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: down, left, down, left, down, up, down, left, right, left\nOutput: down: 3, left: 3\n\nInput: left, up, left, up, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, right, up, right, down, down, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: down, up, right, up, up, left, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, down, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, left: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 93,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, left, down, right, down, left, left, down, right\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: left, down, left, up, left, up, down, down, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 3\n\nInput: left, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 2\n\nInput: right, down, up, left, down, down, left, up, down, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: right, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, down, right, down, up, up, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: right, right, right, up, down, left, up, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: up, left, right, right, down, up, down, right, left, left, right, left, down, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, up, left, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, left: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 94,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, right, right, right, up, up, left, right\nOutput: up: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: right, right, left, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, up, right, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: up, right, down, right, up, left, right, up, left, right, left\nOutput: up: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, down, down, left, up, right, down, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, right, left, down, up, up, up, down, down, up, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 2\n\nInput: right, down, right, left, right, up, right, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 1, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 95,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, down, up, left, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: right, down, down, right, down, down\nOutput: down: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down, left, right, left, down, down\nOutput: down: 4, left: 1\n\nInput: right, left, left, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: down, right, left, up, right, down, right, right, down, down, left\nOutput: down: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, down, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, left, right, left, left\nOutput: down: 3, left: 2\n\nInput: down, right, right, down, up, right, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 0, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, up, down, up, down, right, left, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 96,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, left, left, down, down, right, right, up, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, down, right, up, down, down, left, left, up, left\nOutput: down: 2, left: 3\n\nInput: down, up, down, left, up, down, right, up, left, down, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 2\n\nInput: left, up, down, right, right, down, down, right, left, up, up, down, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: right, up, right, up, down, left, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, right, left, down, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: up, right, up, down, down, up, down, left, down, left, right, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: right, down, right, down, down, down, right, right\nOutput: down: 4, right: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, up, up, left, left, down, left, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, left: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 97,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, left, down, right, left, up, right, down, down, right, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, down, right, up\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: up, left, down, left, down, left, right, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 2\n\nInput: down, right, up, up, up, right, up, left, right, left, right, left\nOutput: up: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: right, down, left, down, down, down, right, up, left, right\nOutput: down: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: left, left, right, right, down, left, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 2\n\nInput: left, down, down, left, down, right, left, left, down, right\nOutput: down: 4, left: 2\n\nInput: up, up, left, left, left, right, down, up, up, right, down\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, left, down, down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 4, left: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 98,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, right, right, up, down, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 0, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, left, up, right, up, left, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, right, down, left, down, right, right\nOutput: down: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: up, up, up, down, right, right, down, left, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: right, up, up, up, down, up, down, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, up, down, down, left, down, right, up, right, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, up, down, left, left, left, up, left, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, left: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, left, left, up, left, up, up, up, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, left: 4"
    },
    {
        "uid": 99,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, right, down, down, right, left, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, left, down, right\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, down, down, up, right, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, right, up, right, left, right, down, up\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, down, right, left, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: \nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: up, up, left, down, up, left, down, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, left: 3\n\nInput: right, down, up, right, left, right, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, left, right, up, up, up, left, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 4, left: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 100,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, up, down, down, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 3\n\nInput: down, left, right, down, left, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, right, up, right, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, left, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, left, left, up, left, down, up\nOutput: down: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: up, down, down, left, left, left, down, up, up, up, left, right\nOutput: up: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: down, up, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, right, left, right, up, right, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, left, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 4, left: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 101,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, right, right, right, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 4\n\nInput: right, right, right, left, up, up, left, down, right, up\nOutput: up: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: left, down, left, down, right, right, down, down, right\nOutput: down: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, down, right, right, up, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: up, left, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: left, down, up, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 2\n\nInput: down, left, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, down, left, left, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, left: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 102,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, right, down, right, left, left, left, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, left, down, up, left, down, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: right, right, left, left, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: left, down, right, right, left, right, down, left, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: up, up, down, up, down, up, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, right, left, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: left, up, up, left, down, up, left, up, left\nOutput: up: 3, left: 4\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, down, left, right, left, right, down, right, up, up, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 103,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, down, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, down, right, down, left, down, right, left, up\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: down, up, left, up, left, up, left, left, down\nOutput: up: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: down, right, right, right, right, up, up, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, right: 4\n\nInput: right, right, right, up, down, down, right, down, down\nOutput: down: 3, right: 4\n\nInput: up, right, up, right, up, down, up, left\nOutput: up: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, left, right, down, left, left, down, up, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: left, left, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, right, left, right, right, up, left, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 104,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, right, down, down, up, left\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: left, left, right, up, up, left, right, down, down, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: up, left, right, down, left, right, up, right, down, down, right, left, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, down, left, left, right\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, down, down, up, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: right, left, up, up, up, left, down, down\nOutput: up: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: left, down, right, left, left, down, up, up, down, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: up, right, right, left, right, left, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, right: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 105,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, left, down, down, right, right, down, up, right, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, right, left, left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: down, left, up, left, right, left, down, right, right, down, left, down, right, up\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, left, left, left, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: right, right, left, up, right, right, left, left, left, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: left, right, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, left, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: down, up, down, left, right, left, right, up, right, up, up, left, right\nOutput: up: 2, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, left, left, up, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, left: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 106,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, up, left, up, down, left, right, down, up, left, right, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: left, right, up, up, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: down, left, left, up, right, right, down, left, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, down, left, down, right, right, right, right\nOutput: down: 4, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, down, down, left, left, left, right, down, down\nOutput: down: 4, left: 2\n\nInput: left, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, left, right, right, up, left, left, down, right, right, left\nOutput: down: 3, left: 0\n\nInput: right, down, left, up, down, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, up, left, left, down, up, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 2, left: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 107,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: up, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: up, left, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 3, left: 2\n\nInput: left, left, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 3\n\nInput: left, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, down, right, up, left, left, right, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, left, left, up, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: right, up, up, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 3, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 0, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 108,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, down, right, up, down, right, right, left, up, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: right, left, up, left, up, right, right, up, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\nInput: right, left, right, down, left, right, left, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, up, right, down, right, right, left, down, left, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: down, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: down, down, down, right\nOutput: down: 3, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, left, up, up, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 3, left: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 109,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, down, up, up, right, down, right, down, right, up, right, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: down, up, up, down, down, up, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, up, right, up, down, right, right, left, down, down, up\nOutput: down: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, down, up, right, down, down, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: right, left, right, right, left, up, right, down\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down, down, left, left, down\nOutput: down: 4, left: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, left, left, down, right, left, left, right, right, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 110,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, left, right, up, left, up, down, left, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 2\n\nInput: right, up, down, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, right, up, up, right, up, left, up, left\nOutput: up: 4, left: 2\n\nInput: right, right, up, up, up, left, right, left, down, right, left, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, left, up, up, up, right, up, down, right, down\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, right, down, left, right, right, down, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, right, down, right, left, up, right, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: down, down, left, left, left, up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: up, right, down, down, up, down, up, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 111,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, up, up, down, right, right, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 2, right: 3\n\nInput: up, up, right, left, left, down, down, left, down, right, left, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 0, left: 2\n\nInput: up, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, up, down, up, up, left, left, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: up, left, right, left, up, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, up, left, left, right, right, down, left, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: right, down, up, up, down\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, up, down, down, down, up, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 112,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, down, down, left, up, up, right, left, down, up, right, up, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: down, right, right, right, left, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: up, down, up, right, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\nInput: up, right, left, up, down, right, up, down, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, down, down, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: left, down, up, up, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, right, up, down\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: left, left, up, right, up, up, left, down\nOutput: up: 2, left: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, up, up, down, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, right: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 113,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: down, left, down, left, down, right, up, left, up, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 2\n\nInput: right, left, right, down, down, left, left, right, left, right\nOutput: down: 2, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, left, left, left, right, up, down, right, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: down, right, down\nOutput: down: 2, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, up, left, down, up, down, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: left, right, up, right, left, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: left, right, up, right, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, left: 0"
    },
    {
        "uid": 114,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, up, left, down, right\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: left, right, right, right, right, up, left, left, up, up, left, up\nOutput: up: 4, left: 0\n\nInput: left, left, up, down, down, left, up, up, left\nOutput: up: 1, left: 4\n\nInput: up, up, up, up, left, left\nOutput: up: 4, left: 2\n\nInput: right, left, left, right, up\nOutput: up: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: right, down, left, down, left, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 1\n\nInput: right, up, left, left, left, down, right, down, down\nOutput: down: 2, left: 1\n\nInput: up, left, up, right, right, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 2, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, left, right, down, down, left, right, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 115,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: left, right, right, up, right, down, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: left, up, down, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: right, up, right, up, right, up, right, up\nOutput: up: 4, right: 4\n\nInput: down, left, left, up, down, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 4\n\nInput: left, left, right, right, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: up, left, right, left, down, down, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 2, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, down, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: left, up, down, left, right, up, up, right, left, down, right, left, down\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, down, right, left, down, left, right, right, down\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 3, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 116,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: right, up, left, right, right, right, left, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: right, left, down, right, right\nOutput: down: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, up, left, down, right, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 3, right: 1\n\nInput: up, up, right, down, down, right, right, left, left, left, up, down, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: right, up, right, up, left, up, right, left, up, right, left\nOutput: up: 4, right: 1\n\nInput: up, right, down, down, up, down, up\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: up, down, right, down, down, right, right, down, right, left\nOutput: down: 3, right: 3\n\nInput: left, up, up, right, left, down, left, up, left\nOutput: up: 2, left: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, right: 1"
    },
    {
        "uid": 117,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, right, right, left, down, right, right, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 3\n\nInput: down, down, right, right, down, right, down, left\nOutput: down: 4, right: 2\n\nInput: down, left, down, left, left, down\nOutput: down: 3, left: 3\n\nInput: up, left, up, up, up\nOutput: up: 4, left: 1\n\nInput: down, left, down, left, up, up, down, left, down, up\nOutput: down: 1, left: 3\n\nInput: right, left, down, left, right, left\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: right, left, up, up, down, down, left, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 1\n\nInput: left, up, down, right, down, right, left, up, left, up, down, right, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: right, up, down, down, up, right, up, up, down, right\nOutput: ",
        "label": "up: 1, right: 3"
    },
    {
        "uid": 118,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: up, left, left, down, up, left, left, down, up, right, down, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 2\n\nInput: down, right, right, left, up, left, up, up, down, up, down, left, right, down, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: down, down, up, up, right, up, down, down, left, left, up\nOutput: up: 0, left: 1\n\nInput: right, left, right, right, left, right, down, left, up, down\nOutput: down: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, left, right, left, down, down, right, down\nOutput: down: 3, right: 2\n\nInput: up, left, right, right, down, down, down, up, down, right\nOutput: down: 2, right: 2\n\nInput: left, left, right, left, right, right, down\nOutput: down: 1, left: 0\n\nInput: up, down, down, down, right, right\nOutput: down: 2, right: 2\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, down, down, left, up, right, right, right, up\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 1, right: 2"
    },
    {
        "uid": 119,
        "task": "count_or_navigation",
        "task_type": "navigation-middle",
        "examples": "Input: down, left, up, down, left, down, left\nOutput: down: 2, left: 3\n\nInput: right, right, right, left, left, right\nOutput: up: 0, right: 2\n\nInput: down, left, right, down, left, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 0, left: 0\n\nInput: up, left, right, down, right, right, up\nOutput: up: 1, right: 2\n\nInput: up, down, up, up, down, right, left, right, left, down, left, left\nOutput: up: 0, left: 2\n\nInput: down, up, down, up, right, right, down, left, up\nOutput: up: 0, right: 1\n\nInput: up, down, down, up, up, right\nOutput: up: 1, right: 1\n\nInput: right, right, up, up, up, right, left, up, right\nOutput: up: 4, right: 3\n\n",
        "prompt": "Input: down, right, up, right, down, up, down, left, down, left, right, left\nOutput: ",
        "label": "down: 2, left: 0"
    }
]